const tasks = [
  {
    question: 'Which city is the capital of Belarus?',
    answer: 'minsk',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country looks like a boot?',
    answer: 'italy',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which is the southernmost continent?',
    answer: 'antarctida',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which river is the longest on Earth?',
    answer: 'amazon',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which mountain is the highest on Earth?',
    answer: 'everest',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which city is the capital of France?',
    answer: 'paris',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which city is the capital of Germany?',
    answer: 'berlin',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which city is the capital of Russia?',
    answer: 'moscow',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country occupies a whole continent?',
    answer: 'australia',
  },
  {
    question: 'On which continent is the desert of Sahara?',
    answer: 'africa',
  },

];
export default tasks;
